Gabriel Adams Bogar

Greater Atlanta Area

gabeab34@gmail.com / 404-840-5850 | Portfolio: https://gabeab34.github.io/gab-portfolio/ | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/gabriel-adams-bogar-2481aa99/ | GitHub: https://github.com/gabeab34

Statement:

Full-stack developer with previous experience interacting directly with clients, making sure expectations become reality. A master of meeting strict deadlines under pressure, as well as collaborating with others' ideas and skill sets. Earned bootcamp certification in full stack development through the Georgia Institute of Technology, focusing on web design. Adept at creating applications that are intuitive and easy to use for people of different technological proficiencies.

Coding Projects:

- View-From-Here Deployment link: https://viewfromhere.herokuapp.com/
 - o **Github:** https://github.com/MMMPhoto/View-From-Here

This project uses technologies and packages from the MERN stack to take user uploaded photos and put them on a google map component using the gps data stored in the exif file. Users can save photos to their profile page when logged in. Uses the full MERN stack, as well as packages from Cloudinary and Google Maps.

- Event-Finder Deployment link: https://mmmphoto.github.io/Event-Finder/
 - Github: https://github.com/MMMPhoto/event-finder

This application allows you to search for events, based on your current location or from the pre-populated list of cities in the drop down menu. Also has filters based on event type, the radius from your location, and the date you wish to go to an event. Uses HTML, CSS, JQuery, as well as Leafly and Ticketmaster APIs.

Technical Proficiencies

Programming-

Attended full-stack coding program at Georgia Tech to expand my skill set and portfolio. Learned a variety of technologies and programming languages in a fast-paced bootcamp program, including:

- Languages: JavaScript ES6+, CSS, HTML5
- o Applications: GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, Heroku
- o Tools: Express, React, Node, Handlebars, JQuery, Bootstrap

Film and Production Experience

Performed the majority of the editing, graphics, effects and mastering of the short film Extraction Blues. Edited together a concise narrative clocking in at 40 minutes from over 20 hours of footage. Designed and implemented the special effects present in the film. Designed and created the credits sequence. Removed grain present using mastering tools. Extensive use and cross-implementation of the Adobe Creative Suite, specifically Premiere, After Effects and Photoshop.

Teaser - https://vimeo.com/138710502 | Trailer - https://vimeo.com/172048510 | Full Movie - https://vimeo.com/174963205/9ec0fc9bc8

Previous Work Experience

Track Seven Events (2013-2022) Norcross, GA

Warehouse Operations and Equipment Manager at Track Seven Events (2017- April 2022)

- Responsible for two warehouses and the inventory contained within each
- Repaired and maintained our inventory of lighting, audio equipment, props, furniture, signage, etc.
- Constructed shelving, support slats and other storage projects as needed.
- Prepared for and managed inventory for days with 10+ events all going on a single day.
- Managed and supervised up to 20 employees at once
- Ensured that clients were satisfied and eager to retain our services in the future.
- Planned for and executed gear flips during busy weeks where inventory had to be returned and immediately sent out again
- Set up multiple rooms for players, staff and media each year attending the Chick-Fil-A Peach Bowl, a six-figure event that took place in high-end hotels in downtown Atlanta. This event took several months of planning and prepping gear every year and required 70+ hour work weeks.

Event Manager and Staff Leader at Track Seven Events (2015-2017) Norcross, GA

Ensured the execution of our events in a professional, safe, and efficient manner. Worked with our clients, DJs, and venue staff to make sure that expectations were met and surpassed. Responsible for instructing and directing workers to ensure that events were set up and broken down safely and punctually. Interpreted, implemented, and adjusted floor plans to best fit the event and venue. Created, edited and produced two event timelapses and assorted video clips that have been posted on the company website to advertise our services.

https://vimeo.com/221819272 | https://vimeo.com/207341761

Education:

- Georgia Tech full-stack coding program April 2022 October 2022 gained a certificate upon graduation.
- Georgia State University 2009-2013 with Honors from the Honors College, BA in Film and Video,
 Minor in Political Science Cum Laude